jemamedia.com 2011-12-03

# Untitled Document

**Jema Media Privacy Policy**

## Our Commitment

JEMA Media understands how important it is to keep your personal information confidential, especially online. Our commitment to protecting your privacy is outlined in the policies below. Because our privacy policy may be updated periodically, we encourage you to review these pages on a regular basis.

## Information Collected and How It's Used

**Your IP Address**  
An IP (Internet Protocol) address is automatically assigned to your computer every time you establish a connection on the Internet. JEMA Media uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site. JEMA Media does not link your IP address to any identifiable personal information.

**Cookies**  
In computer language, a cookie is used to store data on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to store your e-mail ID on your computer so that you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit JEMA Media. We never use cookies to capture or contain personal information from your computer. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. The only personal information JEMA Media has is the information you have provided.

**Your Account**  
JEMA Media can obtain access to your name, e-mail address and other contact information only (1) when you become an advertiser with JEMA Media , provide comments, submit a problem, or request information from JEMA Media and provide your name or return contact information, or (2) in connection with special offers or contests. Contact information provided in connection with problems, comments or requests is used only to respond to those problems, comments or requests. 

Upon registration in the JEMA Media Private Label Account Management system, advertisers are requested to provide company, contact and credit card information. This information is primarily used to identify the account and correspond to the account holder in regard to payments, credits, problems and questions. Credit Card information is provided to credit card processors for the sole purpose of verifying that the credit card is valid and to authorize purchases or to administer refunds to cancelled accounts. Secondary uses of the information provided are to assist JEMA Media staff in detecting and tracking any potential fraud.

**Additional Information Collected**  
Any personal correspondence you send to us, including e-mail and letters, as well as correspondence from other customers or third parties about your activities or postings pertaining to JEMA Media, and all entries made by you onto our site may be collected and stored. Any notes, ideas, suggestions, or other material submitted by Users becomes the property of JEMA Media.

JEMA Media may run contests where we ask Users for contact information such as e-mail or physical addresses. JEMA Media may retain a third party company to oversee the collection and correct entry of User's contact information. The aforementioned third party company will also supply and oversee distribution of prizes for such contests. The User information collected during the contest will not be used by the third party for any purpose other than that of running the JEMA Media contest. JEMA Media may use contact data to send Users information about JEMA Media, as well as promotional material on behalf of our partners. You may opt-out of receiving these and future mailings as outlined below.

**Unsupervised Children**  
Children 18 and under are not eligible to use JEMA Media services without the participation and supervision of a legal parent or guardian. JEMA Media is not a site meant for children, and we do not provide privacy measures designed to protect children when using the Internet unsupervised.

**Expunging Your Information From Our Records**  
You may e-mail CustomerService at JEMA Media or use one of the alternate contact methods listed below to remove your contact information from our database provided we have completed all your pending transactions. Please note, however, that information is never completely removed from our history and disaster recovery archives. You may access and edit your account information by logging into your account online and clicking on the "Edit Profile" link.

**Add Delivery Approval/Time**

All ads are manually approved with in 30 minutes during normal business hours. 9:00am-5:00pm (PST) ****

## Disclosure of Information to Third Parties

**Personal Information**  
JEMA Media does not sell, trade, rent, or release your personal information to third parties in ways that are not disclosed in the privacy statement. If we were to ever do so, you will have the opportunity to opt-out beforehand.

**Transactional Information**  
JEMA Media transactional information such as traffic patterns, sales, aggregate data regarding general shopping patterns, and other site information may be shared with vendors and other reputable third parties. This data will never contain any identifiable personal information of JEMA Media Users. For example, we might share statistics on how many customers purchased a specific product, but we will not specifically disclose who purchased the product.

**Legal Issues**  
JEMA Media discloses personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary for the following:

  * To conform to the edict of the law or comply with a legal process served on JEMA Media or its Web site. 
  * To protect and defend the property rights of JEMA Media, the JEMA Media Web site, or that of JEMA Media Users. 
  * Or to act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of JEMA Media Users, employees, or the general public. 

**Other Sites' Policies**  
JEMA Media has no control over, nor does it bear any of the responsibility for the privacy policies and/or content of any sites or advertisers linked to or on our site. JEMA Media also takes no responsibility for the cookies these sites or advertisers might deposit on your hard drive.

## Safety and Security

**Security**  
After we receive the data at JEMA Media, it is stored on a secure server behind a firewall and cannot be accessed from outside the company. All data is secure and is protected from alteration, loss or misuse. The JEMA Media employees who process your order are the only people with access to your personal information. All JEMA Media employees sign a privacy/security policy agreement, which provides legal confidentiality protections for all JEMA Media Users. Any violation of this policy results in disciplinary action, including possible termination, criminal prosecution, and civil action.

When our registration/order form asks Users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), the information you provide is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, you will know that you are on a secure page because the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer is in its locked form, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. We use a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. This company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, protect all user-information off-line. For example, all of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is subject to restricted use in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage.

Refund Policy

JEMA Media will only refund your account when any fraudulent traffic is served on your advertisements. JEMA Media can not guarantee any kind of ROI.  

## Your Consent & Contacting Us

**Your Consent**  
By using the JEMA Media Web site, you consent to the collection, storage, and dissemination of personal data as described above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email or by means of a notice on our homepage.

**How To Contact Us**  
If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy please contact [sales@jemamedia.com](mailto:customerservice@adonnetwork.com). You can also use this e-mail  
address to:

  * Opt-out of receiving promotional offers and updates about the site. Service related emails sent by JEMA Media to notify the user cannot be opted-out of unless the user cancels membership or use of the service. 
  * Notify us of updates to any of your personal account information.
